VITALII BONDARCHUK QA ENGINEER



Personal details



VITALII BONDARCHUK



vitaliib.qa@gmail.com



+38 (063) 433-52-02



linkedin.com/in/vitaliibondarchuk-aa4314247



t.me/Bondarchuk V

Languages

English



Courses

QA START UP - IT Training Center Jun 2022

Video course - "SOFTWARE TESTING".

ITVDN - video programming courses

Jun 2022

Video course - "HTML5 & CSS3 start"

Summary

QA engineer with practical experience in testing WEB programs, APIs and mobile applications, creating and using test documentation. I also have well-developed communication skills, abstract and analytical thinking, and time management skills. I work well in a team, attentive to details, proactive, quickly learn new material.

Hard skills

Processes SDLC/STLS	•••••
Working with the test documentation	•••••
Methodologies for software development	•••••
JIRA (creating tasks, test cases, bug reports)	•••••
WEB - testing (HTML, CSS, DevTools)	•••••
Selenium IDE (recording, editing, execution of tests)	••••
Client-server architecture (HTTP(s), REST, SOAP)	••••
Postman (writing queries, applying variables)	••••
SQL (DML queries, joins, aggregate functions)	••••
Experience	

Experience

JUNIOR QA ENGINEER

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

Internships - MasterDynamix

Testing the TimeTracker project:

- Functional testing of software;
- · Creation a Checklist;
- · Creation test cases;
- · Generating bug reports;
- Working with the Jira bug tracking system;
- Working with DevTools;
- Selenium IDE (recording, editing and execution of tests);
- MySQL (DML queries, joins, aggregate functions).

MASTER OF QUALITY CONTROL

Sep 2015 - Present

LLC "Kozyatinsky meat plant"

- Control over the processes of production, processing and storage of meat products;
- Food quality assurance according to the international standard FSSC 22000 ver. 5.1 (Food product certification scheme);
- Development and implementation of HACCP (System of identification, assessment and control of hazardous factors important for product safety).

Education

QA engineer

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

TECHMISSION - IT EDUCATION ACADEMI

- Courses Software Testing;
- Internship Qwasar Silicon Valley online platform introduction to FullStack development.